ID	Content	Content CN	Note
1	2$Hello, how can I help you? |null$Buy|1$Sale|2$Build|3$Customize|4$I just passed by.|null/0$-1|null	2$你好，需要来点什么？|null$购买|1$出售|2$打造|3$定制|4$我只是路过的|null/0$-1|null	null
2	0$.......|null/0$Where is this?Why am I here? |null/0$It’s desolate here, I have to hurry to find a way to go out. |6-7/0$-1|null	0$.......|null/0$这是哪里？为什么我会在这里？|null/0$这里一片荒凉，我得赶快想办法出去才行。|6-7/0$-1|null	null
3	0$There is an old man. |null/0$Go ask him how to get out. |8/0$-1|null	0$前面有个人。|null/0$去问问他怎么出去吧。|8/0$-1|null	null
4	4$You finally come here. |null/4$I am the lord here. |null/0$ Hello.... |null/4$It looks like you are confused, you may ask me about it. |null$I have a lot of doubts. |9-10-11-12-13$Wait, let me calm down. |null/0$-1|null	4$你终于来了。|null/4$我是这里的主人。|null/0$你好。。。。|null/4$看样子你很慌张，有什么事就问我吧。|null$我有好多疑惑。|9-10-11-12-13$等等，让我冷静一下。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务1-1
5	4$What do you want to know? |null$Where is this? |14$Who are you? |15$Why am I here? |16$That's enough. |17-18-19/0$-1|null	4$想问点什么呢？|null$这是哪里？|14$你是谁？|15$为什么我会在这里？|16$够了就这样吧。|17-18-19/0$-1|null	完成任务1-2
6	4$This is a place without a name. |null/0$No name? |null/4$ You may call it the land of revelation, where the hero was born. |null/0$It is difficult for me to understand, such a mysterious place. |28/0$-1|null	4$这是个没有名字的地方。|null/0$没有名字的地方？|null/4$你也可以叫它启示之地，英雄诞生的地方。|null/0$难以理解，居然有这样神秘的地方。|28/0$-1|null	null
7	4$My name is Fladnag, an old mage. |27/0$-1|null	4$我叫弗拉达格，是一名老法师。|27/0$-1|null	null
8	4$You don't need to know why you are here. But you are supposed to know who you are? |null/0$(Who am I?) You are joking. |null/4$Have you ever thought that you could be a hero to save the whole world? |null$I wanted to be like that, but it seems to be out of reach. |23$Never been, I am just an ordinary person. |24/0$-1|null	4$你不需要知道你为什么在这里。但是你现在需要清楚你是谁？|null/0$（我是谁？） 你在开玩笑吧。|null/4$你是否想过自己能够成为拯救世界的英雄呢？|null$我一直想成为那样的人，但是这似乎遥不可及。|23$从来没有过，我只是个普通人而已。|24/0$-1|null	null
9	4$Haha, young people are motivated. |null/4$And your dream may come true soon. |25/0$-1|null	4$哈哈，年轻人有志向。|null/4$你的梦想也许马上就能成真。|25/0$-1|null	null
10	4$Maybe most people think so. |null/4$Be prepared for the challenges in future. |26/0$-1|null	4$也许大多数人都会这么想。|null/4$做好准备迎接未来的挑战吧。|26/0$-1|null	null
11	4$I think you have already got the answer you want. |20/4$Then let's talk about the monster. |21-22/4$The conflict between monster and human is long-standing,  the whole continent was affected. |null/0$That's right, I always feel that I am very lucky to be born in a small town far from the battlefield. |null/0$ But the abominable monsters have affected lives of many people and I really want to expel them out of our homeland. |null/4$Brute force can't solve the problem, it will only bring more sacrifices. |null/4$On this continent, there is a mysterious and powerful energy called runes. This is also the reason you came here. |null/0$ (...) So, my duty is to collect these runes? |null/4$That's right, you have the talent to control the runes, only you can do it. |null/0$But how do I believe in your words? I am just an ordinary people. How do you say my talent? |null/4$You will know then. |null/4$The monsters seem to have felt the power of runes, so you have to speed up. |null/0$...... |29-30/0$-1|null	4$我想你已经得到你要的答案了。|20/4$那我们聊聊别的话题吧。|21-22/4$魔族和人类的积怨已久，战事持续不断，这样下去整个大陆都会被波及。|null/0$没错，我一直觉得自己非常幸运，能出生在远离战场，和平的小镇里。|null/0$但可恶的魔族影响了许多人们的生活，真想把它们都赶这片土地。|null/4$光靠蛮力解决不了问题，只会带来更大的牺牲。|null/4$在这片大陆上，有一种叫做符石的神秘能量，收集它们就可以获得强大的力量。这也是你来到这里的理由。|null/0$（。。。。）所以，我的职责是收集这些四散的符石？|null/4$没错，你的身上拥有驾驭符石的天赋，只有你能完成这件事。|null/0$可是我要如何相信你的话呢，我并没有表现出异于常人的特质，何来天赋之说？|null/4$时间会让你知道的。|null/4$魔族似乎也已经感受到了这种力量的存在，因此你得加快脚步了。|null/0$（半信半疑）。|29-30/0$-1|null	null
12	4$Young man, too much words are not helpful, you need to explore the truth by yourself. |null$ (continue to ask)|31-32-33$ Leave. |null/0$-1|null	4$好了，多言无益，真相需要你自己去探索，今天就先到这吧。|null$（继续追问）|31-32-33$离开。|null/0$-1|null	null
13	0$Wait, I still have a lot of questions to ask... |null/4$Young main, the knowledge gained from practice is more meaningful than the knowledge you heard. |null/4$You are still too weak to fight now, I will talk to you again when you become stronger. |34/0$Hey, don't go.... You should told me how to get out! |35/0$-1|null	0$等等，我还有许多问题想问。。。|null/4$年轻人，从磨练中得到的知识，比听来的更有意义。|null/4$现在的你还是太弱了，等你变强后再来问我吧。|34/0$喂，先别走。。。。你还没告诉我怎么出去呢？|35/0$-1|null	完成任务1-3
15	0$(suddenly disappeared...)|null/0$Are these words true? |null/0$By the way, what are these? Zombies! Is it coming so soon? |null/0$Cheer up! They should not be my adversaries. |36-37/0$-1|null	0$（突然消失了。。。）|null/0$这些话是真的吗？？|null/0$等等，这些是什么。僵尸！这么快就来了吗？|null/0$振作点！它们应该不是我的对手。|36-37/0$-1|null	null
16	0$Hateful zombies, really hard fight. |38/0$.......!!!|null/0$So, those are just my dreams, is that person and that place really exist? |null/0$And what's the meaning of those zombies? |null/0$Oh, I can not care so much, it is so noisy outside, go out and have a look. |39-40-41-42-127/0$-1|null	0$可恶的僵尸，真难缠。|38/0$.......!!!|null/0$所以，刚才那些只是我的梦吗，那个人说的话是真的吗？|null/0$刚才出现的僵尸又意味着什么呢？|null/0$管不上那么多了，外面好像有打斗声，先出去看看吧。|39-40-41-42-127/0$-1|null	完成任务1-4
17	5$You woke up, it seems that the monster has found us. |43/0$What, I just dreamed of strange things... |null/0$Those zombies' appearance is an emergency, repel them first! |44-45-46-505/0$-1|null	5$你醒了，看来魔族已经找到我们了。|43/0$什么，刚才我还梦见了奇怪的事情。。。|null/0$情况紧急，现在先把这些僵尸赶出去把|44-45-46-505/0$-1|null	完成任务2-1
18	0$It is really a hard fight. |null/5$These zombies sneaked into our village last night, causing many casualties. It seems that we are no longer safe. |null/0$ Father, I just made a strange dream. |null/5$Oh, really? Talk about that dream. |null/0$I came to a strange place, the land of revelation, and met a strange old man. He told me that I will become the hero of this world and also talk about a mysterious energy called "Runes". |null/5$There are myths about those powerful stones, but no one has actually seen them, and even no one has seen their tremendous power. |null/5$In any case, the village was invaded and we must react. |null/0$Maybe that person's words are true. From now on, I need to move towards becoming a real warrior... |null/5$I am so glad that you can have this kind of awareness. |null/5$ However, it is too dangerous outside now, and there is always the possibility of an unexpected fight. |47-48/0$-1|null	0$真是一场恶战。|null/5$昨天夜里这些僵尸偷偷潜入了村庄，造成了许多伤亡。看来我们已经不再安全了。|null/0$父亲，我刚才做了一个奇怪的梦。|null/5$哦，倒是说来听听。|null/0$我在梦中来到了一个叫做启示之地的奇怪地方，遇到了一个更加奇怪的老头。他告诉我，我将成为这个世界的英雄，还讲了一种叫做“魔石”的神秘能量。|null/5$一直以来都流传着恐怖魔石的故事，但没有人真正见过那些东西，也没有人看到过它们巨大的力量。|null/5$无论如何，村子被侵略了，我们必须采取行动才行。|null/0$也许那个人的话是真的，从现在起，我需要向成为一个真正的战士迈进了。。。|null/5$真高兴你能有这样的觉悟。|null/5$但是，现在外面实在是太危险了，随时都有遭遇不测的可能。|47-48/0$-1|null	null
19	5$There is a military camp nearby, which is relatively safe. My good friend Carney is the commander there, you should try to find useful information there. |null/0$(This time I went out, I can't imagine when I will be back.)|null/5$The road to the camp may have been occupied by the monster, so be careful on the road. |null/0$Father, I will definitely return with success. |null$I will go right away. |49-50-51-52-53$I need to have a rest. |null/0$-1|null	5$在附近有一个抵抗者的营地，相对比较安全，那里也有我的好朋友卡尼，或许你可以试试去那里找到有用的信息。|null/0$（这次出门，不知道要何时才能回来了。）|null/5$通往营地的路可能已经被魔族占据了，路上要小心才行。|null/0$好的父亲，我一定会胜利归来的。|null$出发吧。|49-50-51-52-53$再等等。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务2-2
20	5$Take care of your safety. |null/0$Understand. |505/0$-1|null	5$千万要注意安全。|null/0$一定铭记于心。|505/0$-1|null	null
21	0$This essential passage has also been occupied by zombies, and I must find a way to go. |null/0$-1|null	0$这条关键的通道也被魔族僵尸所占领了，一定要想办法过去才行。|null/0$-1|null	null
22	0$This should be the camp that father mentioned, and hurry to find commander Carney. |54/0$-1|null	0$这里应该就是父亲提到的营地了，赶紧去找卡尼吧。|54/0$-1|null	null
23	1$Hello, my name is Carney, the commander here, welcome to join the battle against the monster. |null$ Hello, nice to meet you. |55-56-57-58-59$Leave. |null/0$-1|null	1$你好，我叫卡尼，是这个营地的指挥官，欢迎加入到对抗魔族的战斗中。|null$你好，请多多关照。|55-56-57-58-59$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务2-3
24	1$You should be my friend's son, I am very happy that you can join us. |null/0$ Thank you, I just came to this camp, can you tell me some useful information? |null/1$My pleasure, what do you want to know? |null$The battle near. |60$ Services in the camp. |61$ How to be stronger. |62$ I think I got enough information. |63-64-65/0$-1|null	1$如果我没记错的话你父亲应该是我的朋友，因此你能加入我们我非常高兴。|null/0$谢谢，我今天刚来这个营地，能告诉我一些战况和有用的信息吗？|null/1$非常乐意，你希望了解些什么呢？|null$附近的战况。|60$营地提供的服务。|61$如何让自己变得更强。|62$我想我得到足够的信息了。|63-64-65/0$-1|null	完成任务3-1
25	1$This camp was built to deal with monsters in northern caves. |null/1$The monsters' activities in caves have become more frequent these days, as if something important is going to happen. |null/1$Monsters there are mainly Goblins, which are divided into three types: melee, archer and mage. |null/1$Melee Goblin has higher HP and armor but lower attack and armor penetration. Goblin Archer has higher speed but lower attack. Goblin Mage has the highest attack, but it is relatively the easiest to defeat. |null/1$In addition, there are many elite captains in the cave. They look different from ordinary Goblins. They are very difficult to deal with. Pay attention. |70/0$-1|null	1$这个营地建立也有非常久的时间了，用于对抗北面的洞窟中的大量魔族。|null/1$这几天洞窟内的魔族活动更加频繁了，好像有什么重要的事要发生。|null/1$根据交战情况，洞窟内的魔族主要是大量的哥布林，主要分为近战型、弓箭型和法师型三种|null/1$近战型生命值和护甲都相对较高，但攻击和穿甲一般。弓箭型速度非常快，但单次攻击较低。法师型攻击力最高，但是相对容易击破。|null/1$除此之外，紫色的变异怪属性会更加强大，要小心。洞窟内还有许多的精英-小队长，它们长得和普通怪物很不一样，非常难对付，要注意这些家伙。|70/0$-1|null	null
26	1$The camp provides related services. |null/1$There is a witch in our camp who could heal you free. The blacksmith Marcus is very important to you. |null/1$ He is proficient in the production of various equipment, and you can also sell your useless items at a good prize. Equipment build and customize is also available (cost coins). Good equipment is very helpful. |71/0$-1|null	1$营地提供一些与战斗有关的服务。|null/1$从我这里你可以了解到最新的战斗信息。北面洞窟口有一名老巫师，可以为你疗伤。对面那位铁匠马库斯，是你非常重要的伙伴。|null/1$他精通各种装备的制作，同时也高价回收一些无用的装备，你还可以在那里对已有的装备进行自定义强化以及外形定制（花费一定金币）。良好的装备对你的战斗非常有帮助。|71/0$-1|null	null
27	1$Killing more enemies to improve your level is the most important method of improving your ability. At the same time, you also have the following ways to strengthen yourself: 1. Collect and upgrade equipment. 2.Learn skills and talents. 3. Collect runes that allow you to use more skills or improve one of your attributes significantly. |72/0$-1|null	1$击杀更多的怪物提高自己的等级，是提升能力最重要的手段。同时你还有以下几种强化自己的方法：1.进行装备的打造和升级。2.选择学习技能和被动天赋。3.收集稀有的符石，它们让你使用更多的主动技能，或者大幅度提高你的某项属性。|72/0$-1|null	null
28	1$Your weapon doesn't look reliable. Before you start your journey, go to the blacksmith to get some new equipment. |66-67-68/0$ Ok, I will go. |69-501/0$-1|null	1$你身上的装备看起来不是太可靠，在开始你的征程之前，先去铁匠那获取一些新装备吧。|66-67-68/0$好的，我这就去。|69-501/0$-1|null	null
29	2$Please come in, there is good equipment for you to choose. |null/2$Which way of fighting is your favorite? |null$Sword|73-74-124$Bow|75-76-125$Magic|77-78-126$I need more time.|null/0$-1|null	2$是卡尼派来的新兵吗，快请进，这里有上好的装备供你选择。|null/2$你希望使用怎样的战斗方式呢？|null$刀剑近战|73-74-124$弓箭远程|75-76-125$法术|77-78-126$再让我想想|null/0$-1|null	null
201	2$Whenever you need do somethings with your equipment, come to me!|79-80/0$ Ok, thank you! |null/0$-1|null	2$这是你的装备，请收好，以后还需要处理装备相关的事，就来找我吧！|79-80/0$好的，谢谢你！|null/0$-1|null	null
30	1$Now you are more like a warrior, let's start our training! |null$ I am ready. |81-82-83$ Wait a second. |null/0$-1|null	1$现在的你更像一名战士了，来吧开始我们的训练！|null$我准备好了。|81-82-83$再等等吧。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-2
31	1$The caves in the north are full of Goblin monsters. They should not be difficult for you.Try to defeat them first. |null/0$ Ok, I will go right away. |84-85-501/0$-1|null	1$北方的洞窟中遍布着各种各样的哥布林怪物，它们对你来说应该不是特别困难，就先拿它们练练手把。|null/0$好的，我马上就去。|84-85-501/0$-1|null	null
32	1$Very good, now you have taken the first step. The next training will be even more challenging! |null$ I am ready. |86-87-88$ I need a rest. |null/0$-1|null	1$很好，现在你已经迈出了第一步。接下来的训练会更加充满挑战！|null$我准备好了。|86-87-88$先缓缓吧。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-3
33	1$The scout we sent to the cave several days ago should have come back. We are worried that he encountered difficulties in the cave. This time, I am sorry to trouble you to go deep into the cave to find the him. |null/0$Understand, I will go right away. |89-90-501/0$-1|null	1$前阵子我们这里派出去的探子XXX，已经过了很久却一直没有回来，我们担心他再洞窟里遇到了困难，这次得麻烦你深入洞窟去寻找XXX的下落。|null/0$好的，我马上就去。|89-90-501/0$-1|null	null
34	7$Are you come to help me? I was hurt, and couldn’t go out alone. |null/0$Don't worry, Carney sent me to rescue you. |null/7$Although I am in trouble, I heard very important information about monsters' action. |null/0$ Great. |null/7$This time the number of monsters here was greatly increased because of the mysterious runes. |null/7$A large number of elite Goblin gathered in the cave, which is the main reason why I was trapped this time. In addition, it seems that a more powerful leader monster has also come to the cave to guide the exploration of the rune, but I don't know where it is. |null/0$Great, very useful information. We need to defeat the leader monster before they take the rune. |91-92/0$-1|null	7$是卡尼派你来的吧，我闯进来时遇到了一些麻烦，受了伤，一下子没办法出去。|null/0$没事就好，卡尼派我来把你解救出去。|null/7$这次的深入行动虽然遭遇了麻烦，但是也打听到了非常重要的情报。|null/0$太好了，说来听听吧。|null/7$这一阵子魔族在洞窟的兵力大增，是因为洞窟中可能有神秘的符石。|null/7$大量的精英哥布林聚集在洞窟中，这也是我这次被困住的主要原因。另外，似乎一个更加强大的首领级怪物也来到了洞窟，指导着符石的探索工作，但目前还不知道它的位置。|null/0$太好了，这些情报非常关键。一定要在它们取走符石之前打败那个首领怪物。|91-92/0$-1|null	null
35	7$I think we'd better go back to the camp and discuss strategies first. |null$ You are right, let's go back to camp.|93-94-95$ I think I could defeat it instantly.|96-97-98$Let me think again |null/0$-1|null	7$据说首领非常强大，因此我认为在进攻之前我们最好还是先回营地商讨计策为好。|null$你说的对，我们先回营地吧。|93-94-95$时机宝贵，我认为直接进攻为好。|96-97-98$再让我想想|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-4
36	7$Let's go. |99-100-103/0$-1|null	7$那我们便启程出发吧。|99-100-103/0$-1|null	null
37	1$I am very happy to see you returning safely and telling me what important information you have discovered? |null/0$(Shared information)|null/1$Our situation is very dangerous and urgent. I am afraid that the monster has found the rune. We have to defeat the leader as soon as possible. |104/1$Young man, are you confident to fight with it? |null$I am ready. |105-106-107-501$ I am afraid I still need some time to prepare. |null/0$-1|null	1$很高兴能看到你们平安归来，说说你们都发现了什么重要情报？|null/0$（分享打探到的情报）|null/1$情况非常紧急，很可能魔族已经找到了魔石，我们得赶快解决这个所谓的首领才行。|104/1$勇士，你有信心战胜它吗？|null$我一定能打败它的。|105-106-107-501$恐怕我还需要一些时间准备。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-5-1
38	1$(long breath) Good job, you completed the task before they got the rune. |null/1$This is your reward, take it. |null$Thanks. |108-109-110$Exit. |null/0$-1|null	1$（长吁一口气）干得不错，在它们带走符石前完成了任务。|null/1$这是给你的奖励，收下吧。|null$谢谢。|108-109-110$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-6-1
39	7$You are right, we need to defeat it before they get the rune. I believe you could make it!|101-102/0$-1|null	7$也对，一定要趁魔族还没有获得符石的时候战胜它。勇士，祝你一路顺风。|101-102/0$-1|null	null
40	7$You really beat the leader, it’s amazing. |null/7$Your action seems to have a very positive effect. Let's go back to Carney. |null$Let's go. |111-112-113-144$Wait a second, I still have something to do.|null/0$-1|null	7$你真的击败了那个首领，真厉害。|null/7$这次行动看样子能产生非常积极的作用。我们回去向卡尼复命吧。|null$启程出发吧。|111-112-113-144$再等等，我还有事要办。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-5-2
41	1$I am very happy to see you returning safely and telling me what important information you have discovered? |null/0$(Shared information)|143/1$ Well done. And you not only defeated the leader, but also get the rune.|null/1$And your reward.|null$Thanks. |114-115-116$Exit. |null/0$-1|null	1$很高兴能看到你们平安归来，说说你们都发现了什么重要情报？|null/0$（分享打探到的情报）|143/1$干得漂亮，你们不仅打败了魔族首领，还取得了符石。|null/1$这是你们的奖励？|null$谢谢。|114-115-116$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-6-2
42	6$Please don't, I surrender.|null/6$I hate my job of discovering runes, it's so boring.|null/0$ So, do you have found rune? |null/6$ That's right, this little stone seems no value, and now it's yours if you let me go. |null$Let it go. |128-129-132$ Kill it. |130-131/0$-1|null	6$别再打了，我认输。。。|null/6$找块石头这种活扔给我干，实在是太不够意思了。|null/0$所以说你们已经找到符石了吗？|null/6$没错，就是这块没有一点价值的小石头，放我一马，这石头就给你了。|null$放过它。|128-129-132$杀死它。|130-131/0$-1|null	null
43	0$(Kill the leader)|279-289/6$Ruthless humans, you will lose finally. |null/0$-1|null	0$（杀死怪物首领）|279-289/6$残暴无情的人类，你们一定会输的。|null/0$-1|null	null
44	6$In this case, I will tell you another secret. There is another leader monster supervising me. It should be on the other side of the cave now. And it also have the rune you need. |null/6$It is my biggest opponent, can you help me defeat it? |null$Thank you, I will go there. |133$ I have other things to do. |null/0$-1|null	6$既然如此，就再告诉你一个小秘密。魔族派了另一名首领怪物来监督我的工作，它现在应该就在洞窟的另一边。它的身上应该也有你需要的符石。|null/6$我早就看它不爽了，你能顺便帮我消灭它吗？|null$谢谢你的情报，我这就去。|133$我还有其他事要做。|null/0$-1|null	null
45	1$Very good. Now we have successfully stopped the monster’s attempt to collect the rune. After today’s action, the nearby monster forces will be greatly weakened. |null/0$ But I don't think we can put it down. There are still many areas that are currently occupied by the monster. |null/1$Young people, you are very energetic. I think you can go to the underground base, which is closer to the battle center and has more difficult tasks to deal with. |null/1$ The end of the Northern Caves leads to our underground base. Before you go there, I hope that you can eliminate some elite Goblin monsters to help us stabilize the battle. Fighting with elites can make you stronger too. |null/0$ Ok, I will do it. |117-118-501/0$-1|null	1$很好，现在我们成功地制止了魔族收集符石的企图，今天的行动过后，附近的魔族势力将会得到大幅削弱。|null/0$但我想我们还不能放下脚步，目前被魔族侵占的区域还有很多。|null/1$年轻人，看得出你很有干劲。我认为你接下来可以前往地下据点，那里离战场中心更近，也有更多棘手的任务要处理。|null/1$北方洞窟的尽头就通往我们的地下据点。再你前往那里之前，我希望你能够再消灭一些精英哥布林怪物。既可以使你变得更强，也可以进一步稳定战况。|null/0$好的，我这就去办。|117-118-501/0$-1|null	null
46	1$Very good, you fully expressed your talents. |null/1$ You can start off to the underground base immediately. Take your reward before leaving.|null$Thank you very much. |119-120-121$Wait. |null/0$-1|null	1$很好，你充分的展现了你的才能。|null/1$马上你就可以启程前往地下据点了，临走前我希望你能够收下这份礼物，这是我珍藏多年的铠甲。|null$非常感谢。|119-120-121$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务3-7
47	1$At the end of the cave, you will find our underground base. |null/1$After you get there, you can talk to the commander in the room at the bottom left corner of the center, and he will help you.|null/0$ I am leaving. Thank you for taking care of me these days. |null/1$Well, pay attention to your safety on the road. |122-123-501/0$-1|null	1$洞窟的尽头直达我们的地下据点。|null/1$到那里后，你可以在据点中心左下角的房间里找到指挥官，他会帮助你的。|null/0$我这就出发。感谢你这些天对我的照顾，就此别过。|null/1$嗯，路上注意安全。|122-123-501/0$-1|null	null
48	0$This should be the underground base, there are ghosts in front, it seems that situation is not optimistic. |null/0$ I have to hurry to find the commander. (Commander is in the lower left corner of the map.)|null/0$-1|null	0$这里应该就是地下据点了，前方有魔族出现，看来情况不容乐观。|null/0$我得赶紧找到指挥官才行。（指挥官在据点中心左下角的房间里）|null/0$-1|null	null
49	0$The room in the lower left corner, it should be here. |null/0$ but no one here. It seems that something unexpected happened. |null/0$They should not go too far, I need to find them. |null/0$-1|null	0$左下角的房间，应该就是这里了。|null/0$可是这里一个人都没有。看来发生了一些意外情况。|null/0$大家应该还在据点附近，去找找看吧。|null/0$-1|null	null
50	8$Young warrior. |null/0$Excuse me, are you the commander, why you are here? |null/8$A few days ago, the monster suddenly attacked our base, we lost the fight and everyone have to escape. |145/8$Before we regroup, we have to get rid of the monsters here. Warrior, are you willing to help?|null$Give it to me. |134-135-136-508$Wait a moment. |null/0$-1|null	8$年轻人，你是来帮助我的吗？|null/0$请问你是指挥官吗，为什么会在这里。|null/8$前些日子魔族对我们据点进行了突袭，大家猝不及防，只好各自逃命。|145/8$在重整旗鼓之前，我们还得把这里的魔族消灭赶紧才行。勇士，你愿意帮忙吗?|null$交给我吧。|134-135-136-508$再等等。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务4-1
51	0$I have completed the task and you can now safely return to the base. |null/8$Thank you for helping me, I will call everyone back to the base, where I will give you the rewards you deserve. |137-277/0$-1|null	0$我已经完成了任务，你们现在可以安全返回据点了。|null/8$感谢你出手相助，我这就去召集众人回到据点中心，在那里我会给你应有的奖励的。|137-277/0$-1|null	
52	8$You come here, this is your reward, thank you for protecting our base. |null$ Thank you.|138-139-140-141-142$Exit. |null/0$-1|null	8$你来了，这是给你的奖励，谢谢你保护我们的据点。|null$谢谢你的好意。|138-139-140-141-142$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务4-2
53	0$Hello, I have some questions to ask. |null/8$ I am the commander here, be free to ask, warrior. |null$Battle information here. |146$Monster distribution. |147$ I think that's enough. |148-149-150/0$-1|null	0$你好，有一些事想询问你一下。|null/8$我是这里的指挥官，有什么不清楚的尽管问我。|null$该地区的战况。|146$怪物分布与战斗技巧。|147$我想我可以出发了。|148-149-150/0$-1|null	完成任务4-3
54	8$It was originally one of the largest human bases. |null/8$However, the activities of the monster suddenly increased in the previous period. Our living space now only has reduced to the center of the base. |null/8$Previously, many people find a hidden camp in the relic, which is a good news for us. |151/0$-1|null	8$这里原本是几个最大的据点之一，在此驻扎的人们非常多，设施也非常齐全。|null/8$可是前段时间魔族的活动突然变多，从南边的洞窟和北边的遗迹两个方向对我们施压，我们的生存空间现在只剩下据点中心的一小块地。|null/8$此前有许多据点的人们搬到了遗迹中的隐蔽休息处，在那里或许你能够找到更多有用的东西，但那是个非常隐蔽的地方。|151/0$-1|null	null
55	8$The monsters here mainly come from the north, divided into 2 types: skeleton and ghost. |null/8$Ghosts are relatively easier to deal with, but be aware of the white ghosts with sickles, they are hard to defeat. |null/8$The Skeleton has many different types. Pay attention to those assassins with daggers, their patrols move very fast, and can cause very terrible damage to you. |152/0$-1|null	8$这里的怪物主要来自北面的遗迹，分为骷髅和幽灵两类。|null/8$普通的幽灵怪物比较好对付，但是要小心那些拿着镰刀的白色幽灵，它们的战斗能力非常强|null/8$另一边的骷髅怪则种类非常多。特别要注意那些神出鬼没的骷髅刺客，它们的巡逻移动速度非常快，而且能够造成非常恐怖的伤害。|152/0$-1|null	null
56	8$Very good, I believe you have already understood the general situation, let us start the task. |null/8$Some days ago, the raid of the monster caused us to suffer a lot. Now there are many soldiers who are locked in the occupation area of ​​the monster. |null/8$Are you willing to rescue these trapped soldiers? |null/0$No problem, I will go right away. |153-154-155-508/0$-1|null	8$很好，相信你已经了解了大致情况，让我们开始任务吧。|null/8$前一阵子魔族的突袭让我们损失惨重，现在还有许多战士被关在魔族的占领区中。|null/8$你愿意去解救这些受困的战士吗。|null/0$小事一桩，我马上就去。|153-154-155-508/0$-1|null	null
57	8$Good job, thanked you on behalf of these soldiers. |null/8$The reward you deserve. |null$Thanks. |156-157-158$Exit. |null/0$-1|null	8$干得很好，我代表这些兄弟对你表达感谢。|null/8$这是你应得的回报，收下吧。|null$谢谢。|156-157-158$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务4-4
58	8$There is one more thing that need your help. |null/0$I will do my best. |null/8$ I was told that the old woman in the upper right corner was in trouble and hoped that I could help her. |null/8$ But I am currently entangled in other business, can you take the place of me to investigate? |null/0$Give it to me.|159-160-161-508/0$-1|null	8$对了，还有一件事情要委托你帮忙。|null/0$什么事，我一定全力去做。|null/8$有人告诉我右上角房间的老太太遇到了不小的麻烦，希望我能去帮助她。|null/8$但我现在公务缠身，没法抽出时间，你能代替我去调查吗？|null/0$包在我身上|159-160-161-508/0$-1|null	null
59	9$Poor Veall, come back soon! |null/0$I was sent by the commander to help you, what happened? |null/9$My child, Veall, had run out of adventure a few days ago. But he is not capable of dealing with those monsters. |null/9$Please convey to the commander, I hope he can help send people to find Veall. |null/0$ Ok, I will report to the commander. |162-163-509/0$-1|null	9$可怜的维尔，你赶快回来吧！|null/0$我是指挥官派来帮助您的，发生什么事了？|null/9$我的孩子维尔，前些日子因为气愤魔族的所作所为，一个人跑出去冒险了。但他并没有能力对付那些怪物。|null/9$请你向指挥官转达，希望他能帮忙派人去寻找维尔。|null/0$好的，我这就去向指挥官汇报。|162-163-509/0$-1|null	null
60	0$The old lady is looking for his child, Veall, maybe we can help. |null/8$ I know Veall. He is a brave child. He is very good at hunting, but he often makes some impulsive things. |null/8$ We have to save him. Are you free to do this task now? |null$I will go now. |164-165-166-167-168$I have something else to deal with. |null/0$-1|null	0$老太太正在寻找他的孩子维尔，希望我们能够帮忙。|null/8$我认识维尔，他是个勇敢的孩子，非常善于打猎，但是也经常做出一些冲动的事。|null/8$我们得去救他，你现在有空进行这项任务吗？|null$我现在就去。|164-165-166-167-168$我还有别的事要处理。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务4-5
61	8$Good. Based on my understanding of him, he should not go too far. He should still be in the relic. |508/0$-1|null	8$很好，以我对他的了解，他应该不会走太远，目前应该还在遗迹内。|508/0$-1|null	null
62	0$There seems to be a secret passage inside, maybe I can find valuable clues there. |null/0$-1|null	0$这里面似乎有一个秘密通道，进去看看，也许有有价值的线索。|null/0$-1|null	null
63	0$This seems to be a temporary break for the warrior, go in and see the details. |278/0$-1|null	0$这似乎是一个临时搭建的战士休息处，进去看看详细情况吧。|278/0$-1|null	null
64	0$Hello, I am looking for someone called Veall. Do you have any information about him? |null/10$I am Veall, what do you want to say? |null/0$ (It doesn't take a lot of effort) Your mother is worried about your safety and sent me to pick you up. |null/10$I know her mind, but I won't go back before defeat the monster. |null/10$I came here alone, just want to be a brave warrior. |169-170-171/0$-1|null	0$你好，我正在找一个叫做维尔的人，你有他的信息吗？|null/10$我就是维尔，有什么事要说吗。|null/0$（得来全不费工夫）原来你就是维尔，你的母亲担心你在外面出事，派我来把你接回去。|null/10$她的心意我知道了，但是在没有打败魔族之前我是不会回去的。|null/10$我只身一人来到这里，就是为了能够成为一名勇敢的战士。|169-170-171/0$-1|null	null
65	10$Stranger, can you help me to convey my words to my mother? |null$Fine, I will go back and tell her. |172-173-174-175-291$I think you need to go back in person.|176-177-178-179-180$ Let me think about it again. |null/0$-1|null	10$陌生人，你能帮我向母亲转告我的想法吗？|null$行，我这就回去转告。|172-173-174-175-291$我认为你需要亲自回去|176-177-178-179-180$让我再想想。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务4-6
66	9$What, is he going to defeat the monster alone? Warrior, can you help me persuade him to come back? |null/0$I can understand you. But his determination is very firm, maybe you should give him a chance to prove himself. |null/9$ Ok, so let him know that safety is the most important and be sure to take care of him outside. |182/0$I will. |183-184-185-186-509/0$-1|null	9$什么，他要去打败魔族？真是个自不量力的孩子。勇士，请你再跑一趟，让他赶紧回来好吗？|null/0$老人，我能理解你的心情。但他的决心非常坚定，也许您应该给他一次锻炼自己的机会。|null/9$好吧，既然如此，告诉他一定要量力而行，在外面请你一定要照顾好他。|182/0$嗯，我会的。|183-184-185-186-509/0$-1|null	完成任务4-7-1
67	10$Oh, no. This time I went out alone without hint my mother. It really caused everyone’s worry. I will go back with you. |181/0$-1|null	10$真是没有办法，这次我没有通告就独自出来，确实引起了大家的担心，我跟你一起回去吧。|181/0$-1|null	null
68	9$Veall, it’s great that you return safely. Thank you, Warrior. |187/10$Mother, I have grown up, I hope I can become a hero saving the world, I hope you can support me, allow me to go out and prove myself. |null/9$ This is your own decision, go ahead, be sure to do what you can, and be safe. |null/10$Well, I will definitely remember. |188-189-190-191-509/0$-1|null	9$维尔，你平安归来正是太好了。谢谢你，勇士。|187/10$母亲，我已经长大了，我希望自己能成为一名战士，希望您能够支持我，允许我到外面去锻炼自己，消灭魔族的敌人。|null/9$这是你自己的决定，去吧，在外一定要量力而行，注意安全。|null/10$嗯，我一定会记住的。|188-189-190-191-509/0$-1|null	完成任务4-7-2
69	10$Stranger, you are a brave warrior. I have a request, I wonder if you can accept it? |null/0$I am listening. |null/10$I have always wanted to be a hero to defeat the monster so I ran out this time to prove myself. |192/10$ But I found that my ability is not an opponent of the monsters. Warriors, can you let me join your journey and fight together? |null$ Of course, the strength of more people is always stronger, I am willing to let you join. |193-194-195$ I don't think you should take this risk, it is very dangerous outside. |196-197-198$Let me think about it. |null/0$-1|null	10$陌生人，看得出你是个英勇的战士，我有个请求不知你能否接受？|null/0$说来听听。|null/10$我一直以来都渴望成为消灭魔族的英雄，我这次跑出来也是为了能够证明自己。|192/10$但我发现以我现在的能力实在不是魔族大军的对手。勇士，能让我加入你的征程，一起修炼吗？|null$当然可以，两个人的力量更强，我愿意让你加入。|193-194-195$我不认为你应该冒这个险，外面非常危险。|196-197-198$让我再想想。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务4-8
70	10$Great, let's fight side by side from now on. I am very good at archery and healing. |null/0$ Well, work hard together! |null/0$(Veall joins the battle)|199-286/0$-1|null	10$太好了，从现在开始，就让我们并肩战斗吧。我非常擅长射箭以及恢复法术，希望能帮上忙。|null/0$嗯，一起努力吧！|null/0$（维尔加入战斗）|199-286/0$-1|null	null
71	10$What a pity, take this, which might be useful. |null/0$ Thank you for your kindness.(Get Veall's treasure, recover 25% HP and MP after every fight.) |200-288/0$-1|null	10$既然你这么认为，那我也不能强人所难，收下这个吧，希望对你有帮助，祝你势如破竹。|null/0$谢谢你的好意。（得到维尔的宝物，每次战斗胜利后恢复最大生命值以及最大法力值的25%。）|200-288/0$-1|null	null
72	0$The commander seems to have encountered new troubles, check out what happened. |201-202-203/0$-1|null	0$指挥官似乎遇到了新的麻烦，去他那里问问吧。|201-202-203/0$-1|null	null
73	8$The monster seems to be planning a new attack, I need your help. |null/0$ I can feel the power of the monster near the recent relics is strengthening. |null/8$ That's right. |null/0$I have been fighting with the monster leader before I came here, they are collecting mysterious runes. I think the frequent activities of this relic monster may also be related to runes. |null/8$That could be reasonable, no matter what, we have to start to weaken the power of the monster in the relic. First of all, we may need to defeat some of them and try to find out where the leader and rune are. Warrior, are you ready to go? |204/0$I am ready. |205-206-207-208/0$-1|null	8$来得正好，魔族似乎正在筹划一次新的进攻，我需要你们的帮忙。|null/0$我能感受到最近遗迹附近魔族的力量正在加强。|null/8$没错，似乎魔族又在筹备一次更大的进攻。|null/0$我来这里之前已经与魔族首领进行过交战，它们正在收集神秘的符石。我想这次遗迹怪物的频繁活动可能也与新的符石有关。|null/8$存在这种可能性，不管怎么样，我们得开始削弱遗迹处魔族的势力。第一步我们可能需要消灭一些魔族部队，并且打听有关符石的消息。勇士，准备好出战了吗？|204/0$我现在就出发。|205-206-207-208/0$-1|null	完成任务5-1
74	8$Very good, I trust you. |null/8$In addition, we have a camp in the relic, where the command will be more immediate. After you complete the task, go there and find me. |null/0$ Well, I have been there before. |508/0$-1|null	8$很好，相信你能做到。|null/8$此外，我们在遗迹深处有一个临时休息处，在那里进行指挥会更加即时，待你完成任务后，就到那里找我吧。|null/0$嗯，我之前已经去过那里，我们就在那见面吧。|508/0$-1|null	null
75	0$It seems to be the place where the leader of the monster is stationed. It seems that the leader is not here now. Remember this position and wait for the leader! |209/0$-1|null	0$这里似乎是魔族首领驻扎的地方，看样子现在还没有动静。记下这个位置，等待首领到来时消灭它！|209/0$-1|null	null
76	0$I have defeated surrounding monsters and also heard about the position of the monster leader. |null/8$Then wait for the leader and defeat it, this is your reward. |null$Thanks. |210-211-212-508$Exit. |null/0$-1|null	0$我已经消灭了周围的魔族势力，也打探到了魔族首领的位置情报。|null/8$很好，接下来就等待魔族首领的出现并消灭它吧，这是你的奖励。|null$谢谢。|210-211-212-508$离开。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务5-2
77	0$The monster leader of the relic has been killed. |null/8$Good, so that the monsters' activities here can be stopped for a while. |null/8$ Next we will use this camp as a base to go to the dark forests - the biggest base of the monster. |null/8$ From the ruins to the north, you will come to the dark forest, where the monsters are much stronger than those in the relic. Be prepared. |214-215/0$-1|null	0$遗迹地区的魔族首领已经被我除掉了。|null/8$很好，这样一来，此地的魔族活动可以消停一阵子了。|null/8$接下来我们会以这个营地作为据点，向黑暗森林—魔族的基地之一进发。|null/8$从遗迹一直往北方走，就会来到黑暗森林，那里的魔族怪物要比遗迹里的强得多，而且我们对它们知之甚少，因此在出发之前你还是得做好准备才行。|214-215/0$-1|null	完成任务5-3
78	8$Warrior, are you ready to go to the dark forest? |null$I am ready. |213-216-217-508$Wait a second. |null/0$-1|null	8$勇士，准备好前往黑暗森林消灭魔族了吗？|null$我准备好了。|213-216-217-508$再等等吧。|null/0$-1|null	null
79	0$It seems that it is not far from the headquarters of the monster, be careful. |null/0$-1|null	0$刚出遗迹就感受到了一阵强大的邪气，看来这里离魔族的总部不远了，要小心。|null/0$-1|null	null
80	8$Well done, and we have completed the first step in conquering the dark forest. |null/8$Next we have to face the most powerful lizard monsters. |null/8$Are you ready to the new challenge? |null$I will go now.|218-219-220-508$ Wait a moment. |null/0$-1|null	8$干的很好，我们已经完成了征服黑暗森林的第一步。|null/8$接下来我们要面对的是魔族中最强大的一支，蜥蜴怪。|null/8$准备好挑战它们了吗？|null$我现在就去。|218-219-220-508$再等等吧。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务5-4
81	8$Young man, your growth is much faster than I thought. We are about to embark on the final campaign. |null/8$Before that, the scout I sent told me that there is a monster leader in the dark forest, I hope you can get rid of it. The Pumpkin Knight is very difficult to deal with, we need to have more information before we encounter it, which will help us to defeat it.|null/8$Are you ready? |null$Let's go. |221-222-223-508$Wait a second. |null/0$-1|null	8$年轻人，你的成长比我想象中的快得多。我们即将踏上讨伐魔族的最后征程。|null/8$在这之前，我派出的探子告诉我在黑暗森林一带有魔族的首领存在，我希望你能够除掉它。南瓜骑士非常难对付，我们需要在遇到它之前掌握更多的情报，这有利于我们击败它。|null/8$准备好了吗？|null$准备好了。|221-222-223-508$再等等吧。|null/0$-1|null	完成任务5-5
82	13$You are powerful, but that's not enough to stand in front of our Pumpkin Knight. |null/13$There are 5 monster illusion around the Pumpkin Knight, and it will be the hardest fight if you directly attack the Pumpkin Knight without breaking the illusions. I don't think our leader will lose. |224/0$I will definitely defeat it.|null/0$-1|null	13$你拥有很强大的力量，可是这在我们的南瓜骑士面前根本不堪一击。|null/13$它已经布置了法阵，在你没击败四周的首领幻象前根本无法与它战斗，走着瞧吧，看谁笑到最后。|224/0$我一定会战胜你们的头目。|null/0$-1|null	null
83	0$Commander, I have defeated the last monster leader, and I also learned about the Pumpkin Knight. |null/0$. The Pumpkin Knight is guarded by a mysterious circle that greatly enhances its abilities. To defeat it, I must first defeat some of the illusions of several leaders around it. |null/8$Well done, this time I will wait for you in the dark forest arena before your final battle. |225-227-228-229/0$-1|null	0$指挥官，我已经击败了最后的魔族首领，也从它口中了解了南瓜骑士的相关情报。|null/0$。南瓜骑士由一个神秘的法阵守护，这个法阵可以极大地提升它的战斗和能力。要想击败它，必须要先击败守护法阵的几个首领幻象才行。|null/8$做得很好，在进入最终的战斗之前，我会在丛林角斗场的门口等你。|225-227-228-229/0$-1|null	完成任务5-6
84	8$Warrior, I am very happy to witness your growth. The last moment is coming, are you ready?(If you choose "I am ready.", you will not be able to save before you defeat the Pumpkin Knight and the door back will be closed!) |null$I am ready. |265-226-230-231-232-233$Wait a minute. |null/0$-1|null	8$勇士，很高兴可以见证到你的成长，最后一击的时刻来了，准备好了吗？（点击确认后回去的大门将关闭，并且在击败南瓜骑士之前无法进行存档！）|null$准备好了。|265-226-230-231-232-233$再等等吧|null/0$-1|null	完成任务5-7
85	8$Take this, it will help you in the dark forest arena. |null/0$ Thank you, I will not disappoint everyone's high hopes. |234/0$-1|null	8$带上这个吧，让我助你一臂之力。|null/0$谢谢你，我一定不会辜负大家的厚望的。|234/0$-1|null	null
86	10$You are about to make the final battle. |null/0$Yes, it’s time to drive the monster out. |null/10$Thank you for helping these days, I feel a lot stronger than before. |null/10$Before entering the final arena, I want to ask you to take me to the fight. |null$ No, this is too dangerous for you now. |235-236$Let's fight together! |237-238-287/0$-1|null	10$勇士，马上就要进行最后的决战了。|null/0$对啊，终于到了将魔族驱赶出去的时候了。|null/10$谢谢你这些日子陪我一起锻炼，我感觉自己的力量强大了不少。|null/10$在进入最后的角斗场之前，我想请求你带我一起战斗。|null$不行，这对现在的你来说太危险了。|235-236$尽情地战斗吧！|237-238-287/0$-1|null	null
87	0$Veall, this battle will be very intense, I hope you don't join it, it is too dangerous for you. |null/10$ Although I really want to kill the Pumpkin Knight myself, but since you said so, I will wait here for your victory. And take this, may helpful when fighting. (Get Veall's treasure, recover 25% HP and MP after every fight) |288/0$-1|null	0$维尔，这次的战斗将会非常激烈，我希望你不要加入其中，这对你来说太危险了。|null/10$虽然很想亲自干掉魔族南瓜骑士，但既然你这么说，那我只好在这里等待你胜利的消息了，这个给你，希望能派上用场。|null/0$（得到维尔的宝物，每次战斗胜利后恢复最大生命值以及最大法力值的25%。）|288/0$-1|null	null
88	0$Veall, I need your help to get rid of the nasty Pumpkin Knight. |null/10$ Well, never give up! |null/0$-1|null	0$维尔，我需要你的帮助，一起除掉令人讨厌的魔族头目吧。|null/10$嗯，不到最后一刻绝不放弃。|null/0$-1|null	null
89	0$(Defeat an illusion, the Pumpkin Knight's attributes are greatly reduced.)|null/281$-1|null	0$（消灭了一个首领幻象，南瓜骑士属性大幅降低。）|null/281$-1|null	null
90	11$Despicable human, always making fairless fights, you will not win so easy. |null/0$Veall, be careful! |null/0$ (Veall was hit by a large energy bomb from the Pumpkin Knight)|null/11$ Hahahaha, I will return back soon. |null/0$(Pumpkin Knight turned into a burst of smoke.)|239-243-244-248/0$-1|null	11$可恶的人类居然以多欺少，别想赢得这么容易，吃我这招。|null/0$维尔，小心！|null/0$（维尔被南瓜骑士的大型能量弹击中）|null/11$哈哈哈哈，我还会回来的。|null/0$（南瓜骑士化为一阵烟不知所踪）|239-243-244-248/0$-1|null	完成任务6-0
91	11$Despicable human, I will return back soon, hahahaha. |null/0$(Pumpkin Knight turned into a burst of smoke.)|241-245-246-247-249/0$-1|null	11$可恶的人类，我还会回来的，哈哈哈哈。|null/0$（南瓜骑士化为一阵烟不知所踪）|241-245-246-247-249/0$-1|null	完成任务6-0
92	0$Veall! Are you OK? |null/10$Warrior, I am afraid I can't continue to fight with you. |null/10$Thank you for taking care of me these days, and being able to participate in the fight to eliminate the Pumpkin Knight is really wonderful...... Take this, it may help when you facing monsters.|null/0$Veall!(Get Veall's treasure, recover 25% HP and MP after every fight.)  |240-242-288/0$-1|null	0$维尔！你没事吧。|null/10$勇士，恐怕我不能跟你继续斩妖除魔了。|null/10$感谢你这些天对我的照顾，能参与到消灭南瓜骑士的战斗，真是我一生的荣幸。。。这个宝物给你，希望能帮助你英勇杀敌。|null/0$维尔！（得到维尔的宝物，每次战斗胜利后恢复最大生命值以及最大法力值的25%。）|240-242-288/0$-1|null	null
93	4$Life is always full of surprises. Young people, you finally did it. |null/0$But I also lost my best friend. |null/4$As a warrior, he fought to the last moment and must be very proud of himself. |null/0$ These little stones contain enormous energy. |null/4$Yes, the monsters are still all over our land, and your trials are still endless. |null/4$ Try to go further and help more victims. |279/0$........|null/0$(The old man flew away again.)|null/0$-1|null	4$人生总是充满着惊喜。年轻人，你终于还是做到了。|null/0$但我也因此失去了最好的朋友。|null/4$作为一名战士，他能够战斗到最后一刻，一定已经非常高兴了。|null/4$看得出你对魔石的掌握已经非常娴熟了。|null/0$这些小小的石头蕴含了巨大的能量。|null/4$没错，魔族仍然遍布在我们的土地上，你的试炼仍未休止。|null/4$尝试去更远的地方，帮助更多的受难者吧。|279/0$........|null/0$（老人再次飞走了。）|null/0$-1|null	null
94	4$Life is always full of surprises. Young people, you finally did it. |null/0$These little stones contain enormous energy. |null/4$Yes, the monster are still all over our land, and your trials are still endless. |null/4$Try to go further and help more victims. |280/0$........|null/0$(The old man flew away again.)|null/0$-1|null	4$人生总是充满着惊喜。年轻人，你终于还是做到了。|null/4$看得出你对魔石的掌握已经非常娴熟了。|null/0$这些小小的石头蕴含了巨大的能量。|null/4$没错，魔族仍然遍布在我们的土地上，你的试炼仍未休止。|null/4$尝试去更远的地方，帮助更多的受难者吧。|280/0$........|null/0$（老人再次飞走了。）|null/0$-1|null	null
95	0$Commander, I have successfully completed the task! |null/8$ Great, it's such a great person. |266/0$But, Veall died in this battle, but he still fought to the last moment. |null/8$I hope he can fulfill his wish and expel all the monsters. |null/0$ I will definitely do it for him. |250-253-508/0$-1|null	0$指挥官我已经成功完成任务了！|null/8$太好了，真是个了不起的人。|266/0$只是，维尔他在这次战斗中牺牲了，但他仍然战斗到了最后一刻。|null/8$可怜的孩子，但愿他能够完成自己的心愿，消灭所有的魔族。|null/0$我一定会替他实现的。|250-253-508/0$-1|null	完成任务7-1
96	0$Commander, I have successfully completed the task! |null/8$ Great, it's such a great person. |267/0$ Thank you for the compliment, I will definitely fight until the last monster dies. |255-256-508/0$-1|null	0$指挥官我已经成功完成任务了！|null/8$太好了，真是个了不起的人。|267/0$谢谢夸奖，我一定会坚持战斗下去，直到最后一只怪物倒下。|255-256-508/0$-1|null	完成任务7-1
97	10$Warrior! |null/10$ I am so glad that you can defeat the Pumpkin Knight and return back. |null/0$Thank you for your treasure, Veall, it's very useful. |null/10$ When you were fighting, I secretly followed the past and found its fatal weakness. I think it would be easy to beat him even if it came back. |null/0$Great, so I can go farther with confidence. Thank you, Veall.|257/0$-1|null	10$勇士！|null/10$真高兴你能够消灭南瓜骑士，凯旋归来。|null/0$谢谢你的帮助，维尔，它派上了很大的用场。|null/10$在你刚才战斗的时候，我偷偷跟了过去，并且发现了它致命的弱点，我想它即使再回来，我也能轻松将他击败。|null/0$太好了，这下我可以放心地去远游了。谢谢你维尔|257/0$-1|null	null
98	0$Before going farther, I should go back and say goodbye to Carney and father! They gave me a lot of help. |251-252-254/0$-1|null	0$在出发去更远的地方前，先回去向老兵卡尼和父亲道别吧！他们给我了许多帮助。|251-252-254/0$-1|null	null
99	0$Carney, I am back. |null/1$ I really didn't misread you, young people, now you are our hero. |null/0$ Because of this, I am afraid I still need to go somewhere else to help more people who need help. |null/1$You don't need to take care of us anymore, just go ahead and I am here waiting for your good news. |258/0$ That's it. |259-260-261-262/0$-1|null	0$卡尼，我回来了。|null/1$我果然没有看错你，年轻人，现在你就是我们的英雄了。|null/0$正因如此，恐怕我还需要去其它地方，帮助更多需要帮助的人。|null/1$你就安心的去，这里就交给我们吧，我一定会等你回来的。|258/0$那就这么说定了。|259-260-261-262/0$-1|null	完成任务7-2
100	0$Father, I am back. |null/5$Child, you are amazing. With one person, you defeated the Pumpkin Knight. |null/0$ No, I am not alone. Many people on this road have given me help. I am very grateful to them. |null/5$I hope you can stay here, but as you said, more people need help. |263/0$ I will finish the task as soon as possible, waiting for my good news. |264-290/0$-1|null	0$父亲，我回来了。|null/5$孩子，你真了不起。凭借一人之力就打败了南瓜骑士。|null/0$不，我并非一个人，这一路上许多人都给了我帮助，我非常感谢他们。|null/5$虽然非常希望你能就此留下来，但是就像你说的，更多的人需要帮助。|263/0$我会尽快完成任务回来的，等着我的好消息吧。|264-290/0$-1|null	完成任务7-3
101	0$That person should be the sout sent by the camp, and hurry to rescue him. |269/0$-1|null	0$那位应该就是营地派出的探子了，赶紧去看看他的情况。|269/0$-1|null	null
102	0$Commander! |270/0$-1|null	0$指挥官！|270/0$-1|null	null
103	6$Haha, thank you for killing it, and you reward.|null/0$(incomprehensible)|268-506/0$-1|null	6$哈哈，终于把这个眼中钉除掉了，这是你的报酬，拿去吧。|null/0$（难以理解）|268-506/0$-1|null	null
104	0$(Defeat an illusion, the Pumpkin Knight's attributes are greatly reduced.)|281/0$-1|null	0$（消灭了一个首领幻象，南瓜骑士属性大幅降低。）|281/0$-1|null	null
105	0$(Defeat an illusion, the Pumpkin Knight's attributes are greatly reduced.)|282/0$-1|null	0$（消灭了一个首领幻象，南瓜骑士属性大幅降低。）|282/0$-1|null	null
106	0$(Defeat an illusion, the Pumpkin Knight's attributes are greatly reduced.)|283/0$-1|null	0$（消灭了一个首领幻象，南瓜骑士属性大幅降低。）|283/0$-1|null	null
107	0$(Defeat an illusion, the Pumpkin Knight's attributes are greatly reduced.)|284/0$-1|null	0$（消灭了一个首领幻象，南瓜骑士属性大幅降低。）|284/0$-1|null	null
108	0$(Defeat an illusion, the Pumpkin Knight's attributes are greatly reduced.)|285/0$-1|null	0$（消灭了一个首领幻象，南瓜骑士属性大幅降低。）|285/0$-1|null	null
109	0$I would better communicate with commander before I go into the arena.|null	0$在进去之前，我最好先找指挥官聊聊。|null	null
110	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
111	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
112	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
113	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
114	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
115	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
116	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
117	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
118	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
119	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
120	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
121	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
122	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
123	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
124	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
125	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
126	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
127	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
128	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
129	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
130	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
131	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
132	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
133	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
134	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
135	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
136	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
137	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
138	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
139	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
140	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
141	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
142	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
143	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
144	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
145	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
146	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
147	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
148	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
149	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
150	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
151	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
152	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
153	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
154	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
155	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
156	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
157	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
158	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
159	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
160	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
161	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
162	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
163	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
164	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
165	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
166	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
167	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
168	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
169	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
170	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
171	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
172	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
173	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
174	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
175	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
176	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
177	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
178	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
179	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
180	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
181	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
182	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
183	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
184	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
185	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
186	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
187	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
188	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
189	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
190	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
191	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
192	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
193	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
194	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
195	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
196	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
197	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
198	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
199	0$-1|null	0$-1|null	null
10001	0$It seems not the right time to talk. |null/0$-1|null	0$好像时机未到。|null/0$-1|null	null
10002	0$I should finish the task first. |null/0$-1|null	0$完成任务后再来吧。|null/0$-1|null	null
1001	1$Hello, I am commander Carney. |null/0$-1|null	1$你好，我是老兵卡尼。|null/0$-1|null	null
1002	2$Hello, how can I help you? |null$Buy|1$Sale|2$Build|3$Customize|4$I just passed by.|null/0$-1|null	2$你好，需要来点什么？|null$购买|1$出售|2$打造|3$定制|4$我只是路过的|null/0$-1|null	null
1003	3$The labyrinth is not yet open, please look forward to updating. |null/0$-1|null	3$迷宫挑战还未开放，请等待更新。|null/0$-1|null	null
1004	4$Only the time will make you understand. |null/0$-1|null	4$时间会让你明白的。|null/0$-1|null	null
1005	5$Take care of your safety, I am waiting for your coming back. |null/0$-1|null	5$千万要注意安全，我在这等你平安回来。|null/0$-1|null	null
1006	6$I will never do it again. |null/0$-1|null	6$我再也不干了。|null/0$-1|null	null
1007	7$Thank you. |null/0$-1|null	7$谢谢你。|null/0$-1|null	null
1008	8$You are really a great warrior. |null/0$-1|null	8$真是个了不起的勇士。|null/0$-1|null	null
1009	9$Veall, you must be safe. |null/0$-1|null	9$维尔，你千万不能出事啊。|null/0$-1|null	null
1010	10$I want to be the hero of this world! |null/0$-1|null	10$我想成为这个世界的英雄！|null/0$-1|null	null
1011	11$Abominable human! |null/0$-1|null	11$可恶的人类！|null/0$-1|null	null
1012	12$Young warrior, come to me whenever you need treatment. |null$ Please treat me now. |276$I don't need treatment now, thanks. |null/0$-1|null	12$年轻人，需要治疗的话随时来找我。|null$请为我治疗吧。|276$暂时不需要。|null/0$-1|null	null
1013	13$Abominable human! |null/0$-1|null	13$可恶的人类！|null/0$-1|null	null
1101	101$Are you coming to rescue me? |null/0$ Go ahead quickly. |271/0$-1|null	101$你是来救我的吗。|null/0$快走吧。|271/0$-1|null	null
1102	102$Are you coming to rescue me? |null/0$ Go ahead quickly. |272/0$-1|null	102$你是来救我的吗。|null/0$快走吧。|272/0$-1|null	null
1103	103$Are you coming to rescue me? |null/0$ Go ahead quickly. |273/0$-1|null	103$你是来救我的吗。|null/0$快走吧。|273/0$-1|null	null
1104	104$Are you coming to rescue me? |null/0$ Go ahead quickly. |274/0$-1|null	104$你是来救我的吗。|null/0$快走吧。|274/0$-1|null	null
1105	105$Are you coming to rescue me? |null/0$ Go ahead quickly. |275/0$-1|null	105$你是来救我的吗。|null/0$快走吧。|275/0$-1|null	null