ID	Name	CN Name	Is Main?	Describe	CN Describe	Icon Path	Null
1	Stab Attack	突刺攻击	1	Inflicts three damages to a single target, the damage is 30%/60%/30% of your attack, this skill comes with an additional 50% armor penetration. (Mana Cost : 70)	连续对单个目标造成三次伤害，伤害值分别为30%/60%/30%攻击力，此次攻击附带额外50%的护甲穿透 （法力消耗 : 70）	RateUp	null
2	Continuous Fighting	战斗续行	0	Each time you use a warrior skill, you can heal yourself, the value is 5% of your maximum HP.	每使用一次战士技能可以回复自身生命，数值为最大生命值的5%	Heal	null
3	Fatal Stab	致命刺击	0	Stab attack has an additional 50% critical chance	突刺攻击额外提高50%的暴击几率	RateUp	null
4	Sword Wind	剑气攻击	1	Cast sword wind to enemy target, cause damage(80%-attack), and other enemies will also receive damage(40%-attack). (Mana Cost : 100)	对敌方目标进行剑气攻击，造成80%攻击力的伤害，其他敌人也会受到40%攻击力的伤害 （法力消耗 : 100）	Rash	null
5	Tough	坚韧不拔	0	20% chance to increase your defense by 30% when you receive damages, for 3 rounds.	受到伤害时20%几率使自身防御提高30%，持续3回合	God	null
6	Sword Wind Strengthening	剑气强化	0	Sword wind reduces the speed of the main target by 20% for 3 rounds, while other targets are also receive 80%-attack damage.	剑气攻击使主要目标速度降低20%，持续3回合，同时其他目标也会受到80%攻击力的伤害	Rash	null
7	Blade Storm	剑刃风暴	1	Cast a blade storm, immediately inflicts 30%-attack damage on all enemy targets, and also reflect 100% damage before entering your next round. (Mana Cost : 150)	化为一阵剑刃风暴，立即对敌方所有目标造成30%攻击力的伤害，同时在进入自己下一个回合前反弹100%受到的伤害 （法力消耗 : 150）	BladeStrom	null
8	Like a Rock	坚如磐石	0	After entering the battle, your defense increased by 20%, but your damage decreased by 20% at the same time.	进入战斗后牺牲20%伤害输出换取20%防御力提升	ManaShell	null
9	Counterattack Storm	反击风暴	0	When you are in blade storm, the damage you received will be decreased by 50%, and the reflect effect increased to 200%.	剑刃风暴期间额外减伤50%，反弹效果提升至200%	BladeStrom	null
10	Holy Sword	圣剑攻击	1	Summons a holy sword to attack a single target, inflicting 200%-attack damage, while reducing the speed of your target by 30% for 2 rounds. (Mana Cost : 150)	召唤一把圣剑对敌方单个目标进行攻击，造成200%攻击力的伤害，同时降低目标造成的伤害30%，持续两回合 （法力消耗 : 150）	RateUp	null
11	Shield Shining	圣盾闪耀	0	When you receive damage, there is a 30% chance to make enemy who cause the damage numb for 1 round.	受到伤害时，有30%几率使攻击你的目标晕眩1回合	Blower	null
12	Battle Energy	战斗能量	0	35% of your lost HP will be converted to your MP	你损失血量的35%将会转化为蓝量	Summon	null
13	God of War	战神怒吼	1	Instantly inflicts 30%-attack damage on all enemies, and makes you immortal before your next round, cost 5 levels of warrior fury buff. (Mana Cost : 50)	立即对敌方所有目标造成30%攻击力的伤害，同时使自己在下回合开始前不死，需要消耗5层暴怒印记 （法力消耗 : 50）	Invincible	null
14	Never Lose	百战不殆	0	When you are in a new round, your defense increased by 10% and the damage you received decreased by 5%, this buff has a max level of 5.	每经过一个回合提升自己的生存属性，防御提升10%，承受伤害降低5%，最多叠加5层	ManaShell	null
15	Impasse	绝处逢生	0	Your damage increased by 0.5% for every 1% of your HP lost.	你每损失1%的生命值，就可以提高自己造成的伤害0.5%	God	null
16	Fireball	小火球术	1	Cast a fireball, inflicting 120%-attack damage on a single target, and a 30% chance to ignite the target, cause its defense decreased by 20% for 2 rounds, and this skill will accumulate 2 levels of mana accumulation. (Mana Cost : 120)	放出火球术，对单个目标造成120%攻击力的伤害，同时有30%几率引燃目标，降低其20%防御力，持续两回合，技能会积攒2层法力凝聚状态 （法力消耗 : 120）	FireballShell	null
17	Magic Strengthening 1	法术精要1	0	Fireball damage increased to 140%-attack, and the chance of ignition increased to 50%.	火球术伤害提升至140%攻击力，引燃几率提升至50%	FireballShell	null
18	Magic Shield	秘法护盾	0	Each level of mana accumulation can make damage you received decreased by 2%.	每层法力凝聚状态可以额外提高自身伤害减免2%	ManaShell	null
19	Mana accumulation	法力积聚	1	Consumes 5 levels of mana accumulation, immediately restores 25% of your max MP, and increases the damage in this battle by 10%, this buff has a max level of 5. (Mana Cost : 0)	消耗5层法力凝聚状态，立即回复自身25%蓝量，同时提高本次战斗中的伤害10%，最多叠加5层 （法力消耗 : 0）	Heal	null
20	Magic Strengthening 2	法术精要2	0	Mana accumulation restore increased to 35%, damage increase effect increased to 15%.	法力积聚蓝量回复提升至35%，伤害提升效果提升至15%	Heal	null
21	Mana Restore	回元之术	0	Restore 30% MP cost whenever you use a skill.	每次施法后回复该次消耗蓝量的30%	Summon	null
22	Ice Storm	寒冰刺骨	1	Releases the ice storm, inflicting 50%-attack damage on all enemies, causing 30% slowdown effect for 3 rounds, this skill will accumulate 2 levels of mana accumulation, this skill can only be used when your mana accumulation buff level is more than 5. (Mana Cost : 150)	释放寒冰风暴，对敌方所有目标造成50%攻击力的伤害，并造成30%减速效果，持续3回合，技能会积攒2层法力凝聚状态，法力凝聚高于5层时可以使用该技能 （法力消耗 : 150）	Dash	null
23	Magic Strengthening 3	法术精要3	0	Ice storm damage increased to 100%-attack, but MP cost increased by 50% at the same time.	寒冰刺骨伤害提高至100%攻击力，但蓝耗增加50%	Dash	null
24	Rapid Cast	急速施法	0	Improve the speed of mana accumulating, the magical normal attack provides 2 levels, and the magical damage skill(except firebird) provides 3 levels.	提高法力凝聚速度，法师普攻提供2层，法师伤害技能提供3层	FireballShell	null
25	Lightning Ball	雷电法阵	1	Releases a lightning ball that inflicts 30%-attack damage to all enemies from the current round, and a 20% chance to cause enemy numb of 1 round, the lightning ball continues for 3 rounds, and this skill will accumulate 2 levels of mana accumulation, this skill can only be used when your mana accumulation buff level is more than 5. (Mana Cost : 150)	释放一个雷电法阵，从当前回合起每个你的回合对所有敌方单位造成30%攻击力的伤害，并且20%几率施加晕眩1回合Buff，法阵持续三回合，技能会积攒2层法力凝聚状态，法力凝聚高于5层时可以使用该技能 （法力消耗 : 150）	Thunder	null
26	Magic Strengthening 4	法术精要4	0	Lightning ball's damage increased to 50%-attack, and the duration of the ball increased to 4 rounds.	雷电法阵伤害提高至50%攻击力，同时持续时间增加一回合	Thunder	null
27	Prepared Attack	蓄势待发	0	Whenever magical skill is released 2 times, all damage caused in the next round is increased by 50%.	每释放2次法师技能，下1回合造成的所有伤害提升50%	God	null
28	Firebird	火鸟突袭	1	Releases a fatal firebird that deals 400%-attack damage to a single enemy. This skill can only be used when your mana accumulation buff level is more than 10. (Mana Cost : 300)	释放致命的火鸟，对单个目标造成400%攻击力的伤害，法力凝聚状态高于10层时可以使用该技能 （法力消耗 : 300）	FireBird	null
29	Magic Strengthening 5	法术精要5	0	Reduces the mana cost of firebird by 30%. Extra Effect - When all of the 5 magic strengthening talents are learned, you only need 3 levels of mana accumulation buff to use ice storm and lightning ball, 5 levels of mana accumulation buff to use firebird.	降低火鸟突袭法力消耗30%   特性 - 天赋全部选择法术精要后，火鸟突袭凝聚状态要求降至5层，寒冰刺骨和雷电法阵降至3层	FireBird	null
30	Magic Curse	魔法诅咒	0	The damage caused by the magical normal attack/fireball/firebird decreased by 30%, and give a curse buff to your target. This buff will cause 50% of that skill's original damage to the target for 2 rounds.	法师普攻/小火球术/火鸟突袭造成的伤害变为原来的70%，同时对受到伤害的单位施加一个持续两回合的流失Buff，每回合损失该次伤害原始伤害值50%的生命值	Blower	null
31	Thousand Arrows	万箭齐发	1	Cast a large number of arrows, inflicting 50%-attack damage to all enemies, and give an 1 level arrow hurt buff to each enemies. (Mana Cost : 70)	发出大量箭矢，对所有敌方单位造成50%攻击力的伤害，并对每个收到伤害的单位附带一层中箭效果 （法力消耗 : 70）	ManaArrow	null
32	Archery Strengthening 1 - Poison Arrow	箭术精要1 - 毒箭	0	Archer normal attack and archer skill have a 10% chance to add a buff to the target, cause 30%-attack damage for 2 rounds.	弓箭类普攻和技能有10%几率附加流血Buff，伤害等同于30%攻击力，状态持续2回合	God	null
33	Bloodthirsty Arrow	嗜血箭矢	0	Archer normal attack and archer skill have an additional 10% life stealing.	弓箭类技能额外附带10%生命偷取	Heal	null
34	Continuous Shot	穿心连射	1	Continuously cast 3-5 arrows (by random) to a single target, each of which inflicts 30%-attack damage and give an 1 level arrow hurt buff to the target. (Mana Cost : 100)	对单个目标连续发出3-5根箭矢（随机），每根箭均可造成30%攻击力的伤害，同时每根箭附带一层中箭效果 （法力消耗 : 100）	ArrowShower	null
35	Archery Strengthening 2 - Armor Piercing Arrow	箭术精要2 - 破甲箭	0	Archer normal attack and archer skill have a 10% chance to add a buff to the target, decrease the defense of target by 30% for 2 rounds.	弓箭类普攻和技能有10%几率附加减防30%Buff，状态持续2回合	God	null
36	Rapid Shot	快速上弦	0	Speed accumulation instantly recover 20% after using archer normal attack and archer skills.	使用弓箭类普攻或技能后，速度积攒值立即回复20%	Dash	null
37	Wound Tearing	伤口撕裂	1	For each enemy with an arrow hurt buff, remove the buff, causing 30%-attack * buff level damage. When the target has more than 2 levels of arrow hurt buff, it's speed will also be decreased by 30% for 2 rounds. (Mana Cost : 0)	对于每个有中箭效果的敌方单位，移除其中箭效果，造成30%攻击力 * 中箭效果层数的伤害，当目标身上中箭效果超过2层时，还会施加减速30%Buff，状态持续两回合 （法力消耗 : 0）	God	null
38	Archery Strengthening 3 - Ice Arrow	箭术精要3 - 寒冰箭	0	Archer normal attack and archer skill have a 10% chance to add a buff to the target, decrease the speed of target by 30% for 2 rounds.	弓箭类普攻和技能有10%几率附加减速30%Buff，状态持续2回合	God	null
39	Take the Lead	抢占先机	0	Your speed accumulation progress starts with 100% when you enter new battles.	进入战斗后总能抢先发起一次攻击	Dash	null
40	Heavy Arrow	破空重箭	1	Cast a heavy arrow, inflicting 250%-attack damage to a single target, and also give a 3 levels arrow hurt buff. Extra Effect - Exhaustion : After using this skill, you feel tired and your speed is decreased by 50% for 1 round. (Mana Cost : 120)	蓄力发出致命箭矢，对单个目标造成250%攻击力的伤害，同时附带三层中箭效果   特性 - 精疲力竭 使用破空重箭后一回合内减速50% （法力消耗 : 120）	FlameRain	null
41	Archery Strengthening 4 - Burning Arrow	箭术精要4 - 燃烧箭	0	Archer normal attack and archer skill have a 10% chance to add a buff to the target, make it receive extra 30% damage for 2 rounds.	弓箭类普攻和技能有10%几率附加承受伤害增加30%Buff，状态持续2回合	God	null
42	Weak Strike	弱点打击	0	The damage caused by heavy arrow increases with the increase of the level of arrow hurt buff on the target. Each level of arrow hurt buff will make heavy arrow's damage increased by 20%-attack.	破空重箭造成的伤害随目标身上中箭效果增加而提高，每层中箭效果额外提升破空重箭的伤害，数值为20%攻击力	ArrowShower	null
43	Swift Shot	无情连射	1	A swift shot, dealing 80%-attack damage to a single target and give an 1 level arrow hurt buff. This skill does not take up your round, which means you could use it indefinitely if you have enough mana. (Mana Cost : 100)	从暗中迅速射出箭矢，对单个目标造成80%攻击力的伤害，同时附带一层中箭效果，不占用回合次数（可以无限次使用，在蓝量足够时） （法力消耗 : 100）	ArrowShower	null
44	Archery Strengthening 5 - Numb Arrow	箭术精要5 - 麻痹箭	0	Archer normal attack and archer skill have a 10% chance to add a buff to the target, cause the target numb for 1 round. Extra Effect - When all of the 5 archery strengthening talent are learned, the chance to give each buff to your target increased to 20%.	弓箭类普攻和技能有10%几率附加晕眩Buff，状态持续1回合   特性 - 天赋全部选择箭术精要后，各级箭术精要的概率翻倍为20%	God	null
45	Archery master	箭术大师	0	You are very skillful in using bows, damage caused by archer normal attack and archer skills is increased by 20%, and the mana cost of each archer skill is reduced by 20%.	对弓箭的使用非常娴熟，弓箭类普攻和技能造成的伤害提高20%，弓箭类技能法力消耗降低20%	RateUp	null